lyricshawa.com 2018-06-29

# Privacy Policy | LyricsHawa

Our privacy policy is the commitment towards our users who are utmost important to us. We respect your privacy which is basic need for every individual.

As the owner of the this website: www.lyricshawa.com we will explicitly ensure our users that your personal information will never be disclose to anyÂ another person.

Although we may use some basic information of users and collected that information to provide you better services. To illustrate this, we list some pointsÂ below in order to guide you of our privacy policy statements:

**Non-personal information** :

When visitors access our website, website may collect statistical information which includes IP address, domain name, your access timing,your email address,Â the type of pages you click, every time you visit the website.Which are important to provide you better services when next time you visited the website & itÂ should not collect any personal information.

**About Cookies  
**  
Cookies are short text file which are download on your computer or mobile whenever you visit the website, Which helps us to provide you the best content and Â the page which is beneficial for you. We also wants to inform you that you have the authority to block cookies but after that we are unable to provideÂ our best services and it will neither beneficial for user or the website.

**Third Party advertising  
**  
We uses third party advertising services which mainly includes Google, to serve ads when you visit our Website: www.lyricshawa.com. These companies mayÂ use your basic information to provide you goods and services that may be of interest to you but not any personal information.

**Public platforms**

This website makes forums, message boards & comments available to its users. These are public forums and its user responsibility that he/sheÂ will not provide any personal information on these platforms because your every action become public & anyone can misuse it.

**Security**

We provide reasonable security methods to prevent unauthorized access to the Sites, to maintain data accuracy and to ensure the correct use of theÂ information we hold.

**Changes and Updates in the policy**

As the technology and internet resources are always changes, We may alter our privacy policy from time to time to incorporate necessary changes in technology.Â The user should always revise our privacy policy periodically to find the changes and updates in the policy.
